let questions = [
{
    question: 'Which festival does 🎅 represent?',
    option: ['Easter','Christmas','Halloween'],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: 'Which event does 🌱 represent?',
    options: ['Earth day','Globe day','St Patricks day'],
    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: 'Which event does 🏅 represent?',
    options: ['Volleyball','Tennis', 'Olympics'],
    answer: 3, 
},
{
    question: 'Which festival does 🎃 represent?',
    options: ['Halloweeen','New years eve','Independence Day'],
    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: 'Which festival does ⚫ represent?',
    options: ['Hannukah','Black friday','Chinese New year'],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: 'Which event does 📖 represent?',
    options: ['World book day','Graduation','Womens day'],
    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: 'Which event does 👩‍🍼 represent?',
    options: ['Mothers day','Fathers day','Childrens day'],
    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: 'Which event does 🐉 represent?',
    options: ['Chinese New Year','New Year','emoji day'],
    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: 'Which event does ☘️ represent?',
    options: ['Earth day', 'St Patricks day','emoji day'],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: 'Which event does ❤️ represent?',
    options: ['Thanks giving','Veterans day','valentines day'],
    answer: 3,
},
]